<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE PubmedArticleSet PUBLIC "-//NLM//DTD PubMedArticle, 1st January 2023//EN" "https://dtd.nlm.nih.gov/ncbi/pubmed/out/pubmed_230101.dtd">
<PubmedArticleSet>
    <PubmedBookArticle>
        <BookDocument>
            <PMID Version="1">29262162</PMID>
            <ArticleIdList>
                <ArticleId IdType="bookaccession">NBK470395</ArticleId>
            </ArticleIdList>
            <Book>
                <Publisher>
                    <PublisherName>StatPearls Publishing</PublisherName>
                    <PublisherLocation>Treasure Island (FL)</PublisherLocation>
                </Publisher>
                <BookTitle book="statpearls">StatPearls</BookTitle>
                <PubDate>
                    <Year>2023</Year>
                    <Month>01</Month>
                </PubDate>
                <BeginningDate>
                    <Year>2023</Year>
                    <Month>01</Month>
                </BeginningDate>
                <AuthorList Type="authors" CompleteYN="Y">
                    <Author ValidYN="Y">
                        <LastName>Test</LastName>
                        <ForeName>Steven</ForeName>
                        <Initials>S</Initials>
                        <AffiliationInfo>
                            <Affiliation>University of Nebraska Medical Center</Affiliation>
                        </AffiliationInfo>
                    </Author>
                </AuthorList>
                <InvestigatorList>
                    <Investigator>
                        <LastName>Carlsson</LastName>
                        <ForeName>Christer</ForeName>
                        <Initials>C</Initials>
                    </Investigator>
                    <Investigator>
                        <LastName>Cecchi</LastName>
                        <ForeName>Francesca</ForeName>
                        <Initials>F</Initials>
                    </Investigator>
                </InvestigatorList>
                <Volume>20</Volume>
                <VolumeTitle>testting</VolumeTitle>
                <Edition>2nd</Edition>
                <CollectionTitle book="nicepmg">NICE Process and Methods Guides</CollectionTitle>
                <Isbn>9781473119086</Isbn>
                <ELocationID EIdType="pii" ValidYN="Y">330</ELocationID>
                <ELocationID EIdType="doi" ValidYN="Y">10.3389/fgene.2012.00330</ELocationID>
                <Medium>Internet</Medium>
                <ReportNumber>Process and Methods Guides No. 12</ReportNumber>
            </Book>
            <LocationLabel Type="chapter">Chapter 45</LocationLabel>
            <ArticleTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135">Qualitative Study</ArticleTitle>
            <VernacularTitle>¿Cómo hablo con mi familia sobre Gaucher?</VernacularTitle>
            <Pagination>
                <StartPage>1</StartPage>
                <EndPage>11</EndPage>
            </Pagination>
            <Language>eng</Language>
            <AuthorList Type="authors" CompleteYN="Y">
                <Author ValidYN="Y">
                    <LastName>Tenny</LastName>
                    <ForeName>Steven</ForeName>
                    <Initials>S</Initials>
                    <AffiliationInfo>
                        <Affiliation>University of Nebraska Medical Center</Affiliation>
                    </AffiliationInfo>
                </Author>
                <Author ValidYN="Y">
                    <LastName>Brannan</LastName>
                    <ForeName>Janelle M.</ForeName>
                    <Initials>JM</Initials>
                    <AffiliationInfo>
                        <Affiliation>GDB Research and Statistical Consulting</Affiliation>
                    </AffiliationInfo>
                </Author>
                <Author ValidYN="Y">
                    <LastName>Brannan</LastName>
                    <ForeName>Grace D.</ForeName>
                    <Initials>GD</Initials>
                    <AffiliationInfo>
                        <Affiliation>GDB Research and Statistical Consulting/McLaren Macomb Hospital</Affiliation>
                    </AffiliationInfo>
                </Author>
            </AuthorList>
            <InvestigatorList>
                <Investigator>
                    <LastName>Carlsson</LastName>
                    <ForeName>Christer</ForeName>
                    <Initials>C</Initials>
                </Investigator>
                <Investigator>
                    <LastName>Cecchi</LastName>
                    <ForeName>Francesca</ForeName>
                    <Initials>F</Initials>
                </Investigator>
            </InvestigatorList>
            <PublicationType UI="D000072643">Study Guide</PublicationType>
            <Abstract>
                <AbstractText>Qualitative research is a type of research that explores and provides
                    deeper insights into real-world problems. Instead of collecting numerical data
                    points or intervene or introduce treatments just like in quantitative research,
                    qualitative research helps generate hypotheses as well as further investigate
                    and understand quantitative data. Qualitative research gathers participants'
                    experiences, perceptions, and behavior. It answers the hows and whys instead of
                    how many or how much. It could be structured as a stand-alone study, purely
                    relying on qualitative data or it could be part of mixed-methods research that
                    combines qualitative and quantitative data. This review introduces the readers
                    to some basic concepts, definitions, terminology, and application of qualitative
                    research. Qualitative research at its core, ask open-ended questions whose
                    answers are not easily put into numbers such as &#x2018;how&#x2019; and
                    &#x2018;why&#x2019;. Due to the open-ended nature of the research questions at
                    hand, qualitative research design is often not linear in the same way
                    quantitative design is. One of the strengths of qualitative research is its
                    ability to explain processes and patterns of human behavior that can be
                    difficult to quantify. Phenomena such as experiences, attitudes, and behaviors
                    can be difficult to accurately capture quantitatively, whereas a qualitative
                    approach allows participants themselves to explain how, why, or what they were
                    thinking, feeling, and experiencing at a certain time or during an event of
                    interest. Quantifying qualitative data certainly is possible, but at its core,
                    qualitative data is looking for themes and patterns that can be difficult to
                    quantify and it is important to ensure that the context and narrative of
                    qualitative work are not lost by trying to quantify something that is not meant
                    to be quantified. However, while qualitative research is sometimes placed in
                    opposition to quantitative research, where they are necessarily opposites and
                    therefore &#x2018;compete&#x2019; against each other and the philosophical
                    paradigms associated with each, qualitative and quantitative work are not
                    necessarily opposites nor are they incompatible. While qualitative and
                    quantitative approaches are different, they are not necessarily opposites, and
                    they are certainly not mutually exclusive. For instance, qualitative research
                    can help expand and deepen understanding of data or results obtained from
                    quantitative analysis. For example, say a quantitative analysis has determined
                    that there is a correlation between length of stay and level of patient
                    satisfaction, but <i>why</i> does this correlation exist? This dual-focus
                    scenario shows one way in which qualitative and quantitative research could be
                    integrated together. <b>Examples of Qualitative Research Approaches</b><i>
                    Ethnography</i> Ethnography as a research design has its origins in social and
                    cultural anthropology, and involves the researcher being directly immersed in
                    the participant&#x2019;s environment. Through this immersion, the ethnographer
                    can use a variety of data collection techniques with the aim of being able to
                    produce a comprehensive account of the social phenomena that occurred during the
                    research period. That is to say, the researcher&#x2019;s aim with ethnography is
                    to <i>immerse</i> themselves into the research population and come out of it
                    with accounts of actions, behaviors, events, etc. through the eyes of someone
                    involved in the population. Direct involvement of the researcher with the target
                    population is one benefit of ethnographic research because it can then be
                    possible to find data that is otherwise very difficult to extract and record. <i>Grounded
                    Theory</i> Grounded Theory is the &#x201c;generation of a theoretical model
                    through the experience of observing a study population and developing a
                    comparative analysis of their speech and behavior.&#x201d; As opposed to
                    quantitative research which is deductive and tests or verifies an existing
                    theory, grounded theory research is inductive and therefore lends itself to
                    research that is aiming to study social interactions or experiences. In essence,
                    Grounded Theory&#x2019;s goal is to explain for example how and why an event
                    occurs or how and why people might behave a certain way. Through observing the
                    population, a researcher using the Grounded Theory approach can then develop a
                    theory to explain the phenomena of interest. <i>Phenomenology</i> Phenomenology
                    is defined as the &#x201c;study of the meaning of phenomena or the study of the
                    particular&#x201d;. At first glance, it might seem that Grounded Theory and
                    Phenomenology are quite similar, but upon careful examination, the differences
                    can be seen. At its core, phenomenology looks to investigate experiences from
                    the perspective of the individual. Phenomenology is essentially looking into the
                    &#x2018;lived experiences&#x2019; of the participants and aims to examine how
                    and why participants behaved a certain way, <i>from their perspective</i>.
                    Herein lies one of the main differences between Grounded Theory and
                    Phenomenology. Grounded Theory aims to develop a theory for social phenomena
                    through an examination of various data sources whereas Phenomenology focuses on
                    describing and explaining an event or phenomena from the perspective of those
                    who have experienced it. <i>Narrative Research</i> One of qualitative
                    research&#x2019;s strengths lies in its ability to tell a story, often from the
                    perspective of those directly involved in it. Reporting on qualitative research
                    involves including details and descriptions of the setting involved and quotes
                    from participants. This detail is called &#x2018;thick&#x2019; or
                    &#x2018;rich&#x2019; description and is a strength of qualitative research.
                    Narrative research is rife with the possibilities of &#x2018;thick&#x2019;
                    description as this approach weaves together a sequence of events, usually from
                    just one or two individuals, in the hopes of creating a cohesive story, or
                    narrative. While it might seem like a waste of time to focus on such a specific,
                    individual level, understanding one or two people&#x2019;s narratives for an
                    event or phenomenon can help to inform researchers about the influences that
                    helped shape that narrative. The tension or conflict of differing narratives can
                    be &#x201c;opportunities for innovation&#x201d;. <b>Research Paradigm</b>
                    Research paradigms are the assumptions, norms, and standards that underpin
                    different approaches to research. Essentially, research paradigms are the
                    &#x2018;worldview&#x2019; that inform research. It is valuable for researchers,
                    both qualitative and quantitative, to understand what paradigm they are working
                    within because understanding the theoretical basis of research paradigms allows
                    researchers to understand the strengths and weaknesses of the approach being
                    used and adjust accordingly. Different paradigms have different <i>ontology </i>
                    and <i>epistemologies</i>. Ontology is defined as the "assumptions about the
                    nature of reality&#x201d; whereas epistemology is defined as the
                    &#x201c;assumptions about the nature of knowledge&#x201d; that inform the work
                    researchers do. It is important to understand the ontological and
                    epistemological foundations of the research paradigm researchers are working
                    within to allow for a full understanding of the approach being used and the
                    assumptions that underpin the approach as a whole. Further, it is crucial that
                    researchers understand their own ontological and epistemological assumptions
                    about the world in general because their assumptions about the world will
                    necessarily impact how they interact with research. A discussion of the research
                    paradigm is not complete without describing positivist, postpositivist, and
                    constructivist philosophies. <i>Positivist vs Postpositivist</i> To further
                    understand qualitative research, we need to discuss positivist and
                    postpositivist frameworks. Positivism is a philosophy that the scientific method
                    can and should be applied to social as well as natural sciences. Essentially,
                    positivist thinking insists that the social sciences should use natural science
                    methods in its research which stems from positivist ontology that there is an
                    objective reality that exists that is fully independent of our perception of the
                    world as individuals. Quantitative research is rooted in positivist philosophy,
                    which can be seen in the value it places on concepts such as causality,
                    generalizability, and replicability. Conversely, postpositivists argue that
                    social reality can never be one hundred percent explained but it could be
                    approximated. Indeed, qualitative researchers have been insisting that there are
                    &#x201c;fundamental limits to the extent to which the methods and procedures of
                    the natural sciences could be applied to the social world&#x201d; and therefore
                    postpositivist philosophy is often associated with qualitative research. An
                    example of positivist versus postpositivist values in research might be that
                    positivist philosophies value hypothesis-testing, whereas postpositivist
                    philosophies value the ability to formulate a substantive theory. <i>
                    Constructivist</i> Constructivism is a subcategory of postpositivism. Most
                    researchers invested in postpositivist research are constructivist as well,
                    meaning they think there is no objective external reality that exists but rather
                    that reality is constructed. Constructivism is a theoretical lens that
                    emphasizes the dynamic nature of our world. &#x201c;Constructivism contends that
                    individuals&#x2019; views are directly influenced by their experiences, and it
                    is these individual experiences and views that shape their perspective of
                    reality&#x201d;. Essentially, Constructivist thought focuses on how
                    &#x2018;reality&#x2019; is not a fixed certainty and experiences, interactions,
                    and backgrounds give people a unique view of the world. Constructivism contends,
                    unlike in positivist views, that there is not necessarily an
                    &#x2018;objective&#x2019; reality we all experience. This is the
                    &#x2018;relativist&#x2019; ontological view that reality and the world we live
                    in are dynamic and socially constructed. Therefore, qualitative scientific
                    knowledge can be inductive as well as deductive.&#x201d; So why is it important
                    to understand the differences in assumptions that different philosophies and
                    approaches to research have? Fundamentally, the assumptions underpinning the
                    research tools a researcher selects provide an overall base for the assumptions
                    the rest of the research will have and can even change the role of the
                    researcher themselves. For example, is the researcher an
                    &#x2018;objective&#x2019; observer such as in positivist quantitative work? Or
                    is the researcher an active participant in the research itself, as in
                    postpositivist qualitative work? Understanding the philosophical base of the
                    research undertaken allows researchers to fully understand the implications of
                    their work and their role within the research, as well as reflect on their own
                    positionality and bias as it pertains to the research they are conducting. <b>Data
                    Sampling&#xa0;</b> The better the sample represents the intended study
                    population, the more likely the researcher is to encompass the varying factors
                    at play.&#xa0;The following are examples of participant sampling and selection:
                    Purposive sampling- selection based on the researcher&#x2019;s rationale in
                    terms of being the most informative. Criterion sampling-selection based on
                    pre-identified factors. Convenience sampling- selection based on availability.
                    Snowball sampling- the selection is by referral from other participants or
                    people who know potential participants. Extreme case sampling- targeted
                    selection of rare cases. Typical case sampling-selection based on regular or
                    average participants.&#xa0;. <b>Data Collection and Analysis</b> Qualitative
                    research uses several techniques including interviews, focus groups, and
                    observation.[1][2][3] Interviews may be unstructured, with open-ended questions
                    on a topic and the interviewer adapts to the responses. Structured interviews
                    have a predetermined number of questions that every participant is asked. It is
                    usually one on one and is appropriate for sensitive topics or topics needing an
                    in-depth exploration. Focus groups are often held with 8-12 target participants
                    and are used when group dynamics and collective views on a topic are desired.
                    Researchers can be a participant-observer to share the experiences of the
                    subject or a non-participant or detached observer. While quantitative research
                    design prescribes a controlled environment for data collection, qualitative data
                    collection may be in a central location or in the environment of the
                    participants, depending on the study goals and design. Qualitative research
                    could amount to a large amount of data. Data is transcribed which may then be
                    coded manually or with the use of Computer Assisted Qualitative Data Analysis
                    Software or CAQDAS such as ATLAS.ti or NVivo. After the coding process,
                    qualitative research results could be in various formats. It could be a
                    synthesis and interpretation presented with excerpts from the data. Results also
                    could be in the form of themes and theory or model development. <b>Dissemination</b>
                    To standardize and facilitate the dissemination of qualitative research
                    outcomes, the healthcare team can use two reporting standards. The Consolidated
                    Criteria for Reporting Qualitative Research or COREQ is a 32-item checklist for
                    interviews and focus groups. The Standards for Reporting Qualitative Research
                    (SRQR) is a checklist covering a wider range of qualitative research. <b>Examples
                    of Application</b> Many&#xa0;times&#xa0;a research question will start with
                    qualitative research. The qualitative research will help generate the research
                    hypothesis which can be tested with quantitative methods. After the data is
                    collected and analyzed with quantitative methods, a set of qualitative methods
                    can be used to dive deeper into the data for a better understanding of what the
                    numbers truly mean and their implications. The qualitative methods can then help
                    clarify the quantitative data and also help refine the hypothesis for future
                    research. Furthermore, with qualitative research researchers can
                    explore&#xa0;subjects that are poorly studied
                    with&#xa0;quantitative&#xa0;methods. These include opinions, individual's
                    actions, and social science research. A good qualitative study design starts
                    with a goal or objective. This should be clearly defined or stated. The target
                    population needs to be specified. A method for obtaining information from the
                    study population must&#xa0;be carefully detailed to ensure there are no
                    omissions of part of the target population. A proper collection method should be
                    selected which will help obtain the desired information without overly limiting
                    the collected data because many times, the information sought is not well
                    compartmentalized or obtained. Finally, the design should ensure adequate
                    methods for analyzing the data. An example may help better clarify&#xa0;some of
                    the various aspects of&#xa0;qualitative research. A researcher wants to decrease
                    the number of teenagers who&#xa0;smoke in their community. The
                    researcher&#xa0;could begin&#xa0;by asking current teen smokers why they started
                    smoking through structured or unstructured interviews&#xa0;(qualitative
                    research). The researcher can also get together a group of current teenage
                    smokers and conduct a focus group to help brainstorm factors that may have
                    prevented them from starting to smoke (qualitative research). In this example,
                    the researcher has used qualitative research methods (interviews and focus
                    groups) to generate a list of ideas of both why teens start to smoke as well as
                    factors that may have prevented them from starting to smoke. Next, the
                    researcher compiles this data. The research found
                    that,&#xa0;hypothetically,&#xa0;peer pressure, health issues, cost, being
                    considered &#x201c;cool,&#x201d; and rebellious behavior all might increase or
                    decrease the likelihood of teens starting to smoke. The researcher creates a
                    survey asking teen participants to rank how important each of the above factors
                    is in either starting smoking (for current smokers) or not smoking (for current
                    non-smokers). This survey provides specific numbers (ranked importance of each
                    factor) and is thus a quantitative research tool. The researcher&#xa0;can use
                    the results of the survey to focus efforts on the one or two highest-ranked
                    factors. Let us say the researcher found that health was the major factor that
                    keeps teens from starting to smoke, and peer pressure was the major factor that
                    contributed to teens to start smoking. The researcher can go back to qualitative
                    research methods to dive deeper into each of these for more information. The
                    researcher wants to focus on how to keep teens from starting to smoke, so they
                    focus on the peer pressure aspect. The researcher&#xa0;can conduct interviews
                    and/or focus groups (qualitative research) about what types and forms of peer
                    pressure are commonly encountered, where the peer pressure comes from, and where
                    smoking first starts. The researcher hypothetically finds that peer pressure
                    often occurs after school at the local teen hangouts,&#xa0;mostly the local
                    park. The researcher also hypothetically finds that peer pressure comes from
                    older, current smokers&#xa0;who provide the cigarettes. The researcher could
                    further explore this observation made at the local teen hangouts (qualitative
                    research) and take notes regarding who is smoking, who is not, and what
                    observable factors are at play for peer pressure of smoking. The researcher
                    finds a local park where many local teenagers hang out and see that a shady,
                    overgrown area of the park is where the smokers tend to hang out. The researcher
                    notes the smoking teenagers buy their cigarettes from a local convenience store
                    adjacent to the park where the clerk does not check identification before
                    selling cigarettes. These observations fall under qualitative research. If the
                    researcher returns to the park and counts how many individuals smoke in each
                    region of the park, this numerical data would be quantitative research. Based on
                    the researcher's efforts thus far, they conclude that local teen smoking and
                    teenagers who start to smoke may decrease if there are fewer overgrown areas of
                    the park and the local convenience store does not&#xa0;sell&#xa0;cigarettes to
                    underage&#xa0;individuals. The researcher could try to have the parks department
                    reassess the shady areas to make them less conducive to the smokers or identify
                    how to limit the sales of cigarettes to underage individuals by
                    the&#xa0;convenience&#xa0;store. The researcher would then cycle back to
                    qualitative methods of asking at-risk population their perceptions of the
                    changes, what factors are still at play, as&#xa0;well&#xa0;as quantitative
                    research that includes teen smoking rates in the community, the incidence of new
                    teen smokers, among others.</AbstractText>
                <CopyrightInformation>Copyright &#xa9; 2023, StatPearls Publishing LLC.</CopyrightInformation>
            </Abstract>
            <Sections>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s1">Introduction</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s2">
                        Function</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s3">Issues
                        of Concern</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s4">Clinical
                        Significance</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s5">Enhancing
                        Healthcare Team Outcomes</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s6">Review
                        Questions</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
                <Section>
                    <SectionTitle book="statpearls" part="article-28135" sec="article-28135.s7">
                        References</SectionTitle>
                </Section>
            </Sections>
            <KeywordList Owner="NOTNLM">
                <Keyword>NICE process and methods guides</Keyword>
                <Keyword>process guide/guidance</Keyword>
                <Keyword>good practice guidance</Keyword>
                <Keyword>NICE Guidelines</Keyword>
                <Keyword>medicines</Keyword>
                <Keyword>prescribing</Keyword>
                <Keyword>commissioning medicines</Keyword>
                <Keyword>good practice</Keyword>
            </KeywordList>
            <ContributionDate>
                <Year>2022</Year>
                <Month>9</Month>
                <Day>18</Day>
            </ContributionDate>
            <DateRevised>
                <Year>2017</Year>
                <Month>2</Month>
                <Day>16</Day>
            </DateRevised>
            <GrantList CompleteYN="Y">
                <Grant>
                    <GrantID>HHSN263201200074I</GrantID>
                    <Acronym>OD</Acronym>
                    <Agency>NIH HHS</Agency>
                    <Country>United States</Country>
                </Grant>
            </GrantList>
            <ItemList ListType="Synonyms">
                <Item>Gordon’s Syndrome</Item>
                <Item>Familial Hyperkalemic Hypertension</Item>
                <Item>PHAII</Item>
            </ItemList>
            <ReferenceList>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Moser A, Korstjens I. Series: Practical guidance to qualitative
                        research. Part 1: Introduction. Eur J Gen Pract. 2017 Dec;23(1):271-273.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC8816396</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">29185831</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Cleland JA. The qualitative orientation in medical education research.
                        Korean J Med Educ. 2017 Jun;29(2):61-71.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC5465434</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">28597869</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Foley G, Timonen V. Using Grounded Theory Method to Capture and
                        Analyze Health Care Experiences. Health Serv Res. 2015 Aug;50(4):1195-210.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC4545354</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">25523315</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Devers KJ. How will we know "good" qualitative research when we see
                        it? Beginning the dialogue in health services research. Health Serv Res.
                        1999 Dec;34(5 Pt 2):1153-88.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC1089058</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">10591278</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Huston P, Rowan M. Qualitative studies. Their role in medical
                        research. Can Fam Physician. 1998 Nov;44:2453-8.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC2277956</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">9839063</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Corner EJ, Murray EJ, Brett SJ. Qualitative, grounded theory
                        exploration of patients' experience of early mobilisation, rehabilitation
                        and recovery after critical illness. BMJ Open. 2019 Feb 24;9(2):e026348.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC6443050</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">30804034</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Moser A, Korstjens I. Series: Practical guidance to qualitative
                        research. Part 3: Sampling, data collection and analysis. Eur J Gen Pract.
                        2018 Dec;24(1):9-18.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC5774281</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">29199486</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Houghton C, Murphy K, Meehan B, Thomas J, Brooker D, Casey D. From
                        screening to synthesis: using nvivo to enhance transparency in qualitative
                        evidence synthesis. J Clin Nurs. 2017 Mar;26(5-6):873-881.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">27324875</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Soratto J, Pires DEP, Friese S. Thematic content analysis using
                        ATLAS.ti software: Potentialities for researchs in health. Rev Bras Enferm.
                        2020;73(3):e20190250.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">32321144</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Zamawe FC. The Implication of Using NVivo Software in Qualitative Data
                        Analysis: Evidence-Based Reflections. Malawi Med J. 2015 Mar;27(1):13-5.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC4478399</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">26137192</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Korstjens I, Moser A. Series: Practical guidance to qualitative
                        research. Part 4: Trustworthiness and publishing. Eur J Gen Pract. 2018
                        Dec;24(1):120-124.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC8816392</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">29202616</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Tong A, Sainsbury P, Craig J. Consolidated criteria for reporting
                        qualitative research (COREQ): a 32-item checklist for interviews and focus
                        groups. Int J Qual Health Care. 2007 Dec;19(6):349-57.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">17872937</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>O'Brien BC, Harris IB, Beckman TJ, Reed DA, Cook DA. Standards for
                        reporting qualitative research: a synthesis of recommendations. Acad Med.
                        2014 Sep;89(9):1245-51.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">24979285</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Palermo C, King O, Brock T, Brown T, Crampton P, Hall H, Macaulay J,
                        Morphet J, Mundy M, Oliaro L, Paynter S, Williams B, Wright C, E Rees C.
                        Setting priorities for health education research: A mixed methods study. Med
                        Teach. 2019 Sep;41(9):1029-1038.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">31141390</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Tscholl DW, Handschin L, R&#xf6;ssler J, Weiss M, Spahn DR,
                        N&#xf6;thiger CB. It's not you, it's the design - common problems with
                        patient monitoring reported by anesthesiologists: a mixed qualitative and
                        quantitative study. BMC Anesthesiol. 2019 May 28;19(1):87.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC6540409</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">31138143</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Grossoehme DH. Overview of qualitative research. J Health Care
                        Chaplain. 2014;20(3):109-22.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pmc">PMC4609437</ArticleId>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">24926897</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
                <Reference>
                    <Citation>Delaney H, Devane D, Hunter A, Hennessy M, Parker A, Murphy L, Cronin
                        P, Smith V. Limited evidence exists on the effectiveness of education and
                        training interventions on trial recruitment; a systematic review. J Clin
                        Epidemiol. 2019 Sep;113:75-82.</Citation>
                    <ArticleIdList>
                        <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">31128220</ArticleId>
                    </ArticleIdList>
                </Reference>
            </ReferenceList>
        </BookDocument>
        <PubmedBookData>
            <History>
                <PubMedPubDate PubStatus="pubmed">
                    <Year>2017</Year>
                    <Month>2</Month>
                    <Day>18</Day>
                    <Hour>6</Hour>
                    <Minute>1</Minute>
                </PubMedPubDate>
                <PubMedPubDate PubStatus="medline">
                    <Year>2017</Year>
                    <Month>2</Month>
                    <Day>18</Day>
                    <Hour>6</Hour>
                    <Minute>1</Minute>
                </PubMedPubDate>
                <PubMedPubDate PubStatus="entrez">
                    <Year>2017</Year>
                    <Month>2</Month>
                    <Day>18</Day>
                    <Hour>6</Hour>
                    <Minute>1</Minute>
                </PubMedPubDate>
            </History>
            <PublicationStatus>ppublish</PublicationStatus>
            <ArticleIdList>
                <ArticleId IdType="pubmed">28211659</ArticleId>
            </ArticleIdList>
        </PubmedBookData>
    </PubmedBookArticle>
</PubmedArticleSet>
